getu.com 2014-05-25

# Privacy Policy | U

Conduit Ltd. and its affiliates ("Conduit" or "we") respect the privacy of the users ("User" or "you") of the Conduit proprietary browser ("U") and are committed to protecting the information of its Users. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you access and use U at http://www.getu.com. This Privacy Policy applies to your visit to or use of U. It governs and describes how Conduit accesses, collects and uses information that is generated by your use of U and the rights and options available to you regarding your information. This policy is incorporated to the U End User License Agreement (the "EULA") available at: http://getu.com/license. 

PLEASE READ CAREFULLY: BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, ACCESSING AND/OR USING U, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DESCRIBED BELOW). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT DOWNLOAD, CONNECT TO, ACCESS, ACTIVATE OR USE U AND ARE OBLIGED TO UNINSTALL, ERASE OR REMOVE U FROM YOUR DEVICE. 

### Information Conduit Collects and Receives When You Use U

Except as expressly provided herein, **IT IS NOT NECESSARY FOR YOU TO PROVIDE CONDUIT WITH ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION TO USE U.** **CONDUIT WILL NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION FROM YOU WITHOUT YOUR APPROVAL OR UNLESS YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDE IT OTHERWISE .** "Personally Identifying Information" means any information that may identify an individual or is of a private and/or sensitive nature, including your login credentials to a third party website, name, postal address and email address." 

#### Cookies

When you download U, U interacts with the Conduit servers. Information is sent from U to Conduit through the servers. Conduit may allow websites you visit to use Cookies. Cookies are packets of information sent to your computer when you visit a website to allow this website to recognize you on your next visit thereon. Cookies may store your preferences and other information, such as the webpages you have accessed and your session durations. 

When you download U, U interacts with the Conduit servers. Information is sent from U to Conduit through the servers. Conduit may allow websites you visit to use Cookies. Cookies are packets of information sent to your computer when you visit a website to allow this website to recognize you on your next visit thereon. Cookies may store your preferences and other information, such as the webpages you have accessed and your session durations. 

Cookies can be removed or blocked by clicking the U menu (three lines) icon, selecting Settings, and then Show Advanced Settings. However, bear in mind that if you block Cookies, your user experience on U may be affected and some of the U features may be limited or inaccessible as a result. 

#### Non-Personal Information Conduit Receives

When you use U, Conduit may use anonymous and aggregated information collected through your use of U ("Non-Personal Information"). Such information will not identify you personally. Conduit may use such information for statistical purposes, including by making it available to its partners. The Non-Personal Information U sends to the Conduit servers includes the following: 

  * IP address (which also identifies the country of the user);
  * selected language;
  * selected preferences and/or options on U;
  * usage of and activity on or related to U;
  * your Sidebar apps and features on U;
  * U version; and
  * computer operating system.

You may always customize the U settings according to your preferences if you choose not to send any such technical information to us.

#### Uses

Conduit may use the information it collects and receives only as follows:

Conduit may use the information it collects and receives for business and operations purposes including:

To notify you of U updates, to provide you with U functionality and features, to provide us with usage data for statistical purposes, to facilitate our operation and improvement of U, to improve and customize your user experience of U and develop new features; to provide you with support and handle your feedback; to enforce the U EULA; to comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies when we have a good faith belief that our cooperation with them meets the applicable legal standards; and to take any action in any case of dispute involving you with respect or in relation to U.

U may also store bookmarks and browsing history on your computer locally (which means the information is not transferred to our servers). You can delete bookmarks and browsing history information at any time. U may automatically check to determine if you are using its most current version and may, through pop-up boxes or similar mechanisms, inform you if you need to upgrade your U version. During this process, an IP address or device identifier identifying your device and U version may be sent to our Web server.

#### U Features

U is built using the Google Chromium open source code and may integrate certain features enabled by Google by default (such as Google search box, Autocomplete, Translate, Safe browsing, etc.). Use of these features may require the collection of Non-Personal Information of the user by Google and thus is governed by the Google privacy policy which can be found at www.google.com. We may also integrate other self-developed features. To disable any of the U features, you may click the U menu (three lines) icon and change your privacy settings accordingly.

### Information Stored on Your Device

U stores certain information about your browsing history on your computer. This information includes:

  * Basic browsing history information: the URLs of pages that you visit, a cache file of text and images from those pages, and a list of some IP addresses or device identifiers linked from pages that you visit.
  * A searchable index of most pages you visit (except for secure pages with "https" web addresses, such as some bank pages).
  * Thumbnail-sized screenshots of most pages you visit.
  * Cookies or web storage data deposited on your machine by websites you visit.
  * A record of downloads you have made from websites.

You can limit the information U saves on your computer by using incognito mode. In this mode, U will not store basic browsing history information such as URLs, cached page text, or IP addresses or device identifiers of pages linked from the websites you visit. It will also not store snapshots of pages that you visit or keep a record of your downloads (though this information could still be stored elsewhere on your device, for example, in a list of recently opened files). New Cookies received in incognito mode will not be saved after you close U or close all open incognito windows. You can see when you are in incognito mode by the incognito icon that appears in the top corner of U.

###  Information U Shares with Third Party Sites

Whenever you use the Internet, or software with Internet-enabled features, information about your computer ("standard computer information") is sent to the websites you visit and online services you use. Standard computer information includes your computer's IP address, browser type and language, access times, and referring website addresses (the web addresses of the sites you came from). This information might be logged on those websites' web servers. Which information is logged and how that information is used depends on the privacy practices of the websites you visit and web services you use, which are unrelated to Conduit. It is recommended that you review the privacy policies of any website(s) you access through U before using those websites.

If you use U in incognito mode, it will not transmit any preexisting Cookies to websites that you visit. Websites may deposit new Cookies on your computer while you are in incognito mode. These Cookies, however, will only be temporarily stored and transmitted to websites while you remain in incognito mode. They will be deleted when you close U or close all open incognito windows.

### Sharing Personally Identifying Information with Others

We do not sell, rent, lease or license your Personally Identifying Information, to the extent collected hereunder, to third parties for their own independent use. We may share Personally Identifying Information collected through U with others in any of the following instances:

  * Your Personally Identifying Information may be shared with Third Parties in order to operate, maintain, enable and enhance U features and services and to develop other related services;
  * If we reasonably believe that you have breached the EULA, misused U or performed any action that we reasonably believe to be violating the applicable law or rules;
  * If we reasonably believe that we are required by law to share or disclose your information, we may share your information with law enforcement or other competent authorities and any third party, as may be required;
  * In any case of dispute of any kind involving you in connection with U;
  * If we organize the operation of U within a different framework or through another legal structure or entity, provided, however, that those entities agree to be bound by this Policy, with reasonably necessary changes taken into consideration;
  * We may also share Personally Identifying Information with our affiliated entities (entities controlled by, under common control or controlling us, directly or indirectly), but their use of such information must comply with this Policy; and,
  * In any case other than the above, we will share your Personally Identifying Information with others only if we receive your explicit prior consent.

### Third Party Apps, Features and Content on the U Sidebar

Conduit may offer you additional features and/or content that you may add to your sidebar on U ("Sidebar") to improve and personalize your user experience on U, whether upon downloading U and/or at any time thereafter. These features and/or content are provided by our partners, affiliates, service providers and other third parties (collectively, "Third Parties"). These features and/or content may be in the form of apps, buttons, gadgets and others ("Apps"). In the event that these Apps may require the collection of your Personally Identifying Information, the Third Party providing the Apps should present to you a clear disclosure of the information that will be collected, and you should have the opportunity to decide whether or not to share such information or alternatively not use or remove such Apps from your Sidebar. These Third Parties' Apps and the connection to and use thereof on your Sidebar are subject to the terms and privacy policies of the respective Third Parties providing such Apps.

Social Networks. If available, you may also choose to activate additional Apps that provide you with the ability to log in to, view, update and use your personal account on favorite social networks (for example, Facebook, Twitter, etc.) directly from your U Sidebar. During such activation you will be asked to grant Conduit permission to compile certain information from such social network systems to enable such Apps on your personal Sidebar. This information may include friends or contact lists, notes, updates and photos, and may be used by Conduit to help you customize your Sidebar, suggest new Apps that may be relevant to you or provide Conduit with data for statistical purposes. If you elect to permit Conduit to access this information, Conduit will be able to see and use this information and such action may change your preexisting privacy settings in your social networks account(s). Please note that the control over your privacy settings in your social network account(s) is only available in your social network accounts. Please see your social network provider policies for any questions or concerns. **It is important to note that Conduit does not sell or rent any Personal Identifying Information it compiles to any third parties.** You may opt not to grant Conduit access to your social network account(s) at any time by changing your social network settings in your social networks account(s) or by not granting Conduit access.

### Conduit Also Abides by the Following Privacy Practices:

**1\. Easy uninstall -** You can easily uninstall U or any features and/or content from your Sidebar that are embedded on it at any time. To uninstall any app, feature or content from U, simply click the U menu (three lines) icon, select Settings and then open the Extensions list, where you can disable any app or feature you wish to remove from your Sidebar. To uninstall U from your computer, just use the standard uninstall processes that are available as part of your operating system (for example, add/remove programs in Windows).

**2\. Control over preferences -** You have full control over U and can modify your preferences at any time (including the components and features you have added to U) by clicking the U menu (three lines) icon, selecting Settings and then opening the Extensions list, or in the U Sidebar.

**3\. Access -** You may send us a request to access the personal information that we collect through your use of U. We may require that you provide us additional information to verify your identity.

**4\. Data retention -** We may delete your Personally Identifying Information from our systems or anonymize it if we deem it is no longer necessary for our reasonable business needs.

**5\. Transfer of data outside your territory -** U, by its nature as an online service, may store and process information in various locations throughout the globe. If you are a resident in a jurisdiction where transfer of your personal information to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you provide us with your express and unambiguous consent to such transfer.

**6\. Information security -** We implement measures to secure your personal information and to minimize the risks of damage, loss and unauthorized access or use of the information. However, these measures are unable to provide absolute information security. Therefore, although we make efforts to secure your personal information, we cannot guarantee and you cannot reasonably expect that U and its databases will be completely immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unauthorized interceptions or access, or other kinds of abuse and misuse.

**7\. Corporate action -** In the event that Conduit goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, bankruptcy, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personally Identifying Information may be among the assets transferred. For clarity, the information may be retained and used by more than a single entity following such a transition.

**8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy -** We may from time to time change this Policy. Substantial changes will take effect 30 days after we have posted an initial notification through U or on the U website at: http://getu.com. Other changes will take effect 7 days after their initial posting. However, if we amend the Policy to comply with legal requirements, the amendments will become effective immediately upon their initial posting, or as required. You agree to be bound by any of the changes made to this Policy. Your continued use of U after the changes take effect will indicate your acceptance of the amended Policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of U.

**9\. Report -** If you have a reason to believe that your rights have been infringed upon while using U, please contact Conduit via email at [privacy@getu.com](mailto:privacy@getu.com).

Last updated: January 2014
